newsbytesapp.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy Policy

The privacy policy listed below is for the website www.newsbytesapp.com and owned by Elysium Labs Private Limited. The policy states the terms of privacy for users who browse the website. Your privacy is important to us and we take great care to protect it. We do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to any third party without your consent. The website complies to all the standard laws and requirements for user privacy 

We use cookies to augment the experience of our users while browsing the website. The website has integrated a cookie control system using which a user can disallow the use of cookies. Even if you reject cookies, you can read all the content present on the website. The cookie control system complies with recent legislation requirements with respect to obtaining user’s consent. 

Cookies are small files that track, save and store information about the user's interactions and usage of the website. This helps us to provide a tailored browsing experience. 

This website has also integrated analytics software provided by Google Analytics to better understand the users who browse the website. This software also uses cookies to track the engagement. To read about Google’s privacy policy please visit <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>. These cookies usually expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is stored, saved or collected using them. 

The information provided by you shall be used to: 

  * Improve our website and enable us to provide our users the best reading experience
  * Send newsletter(s) to you in case you subscribe for the same.
  * Provide you an opportunity to participate in surveys
  * Provide updates about our services and products
  * Address any security or technical issues

Security

The security of your personal information is of utmost importance to us. We use security tools to protect your personal information against unauthorised access. However, as you might understand. there is no method of transmission over the Internet, or of electronic storage, which is 100% secure, therefore, we can not guarantee its absolute security. Even though we work hard to protect your information, we don’t promise that your personal information will always remain private. 

We use cookies to augment the experience of our users while browsing the website. The website has integrated a cookie control system using which a user can disallow the use of cookies. Even if you reject cookies, you can read all the content present on the website. The cookie control system complies with recent legislation requirements with respect to obtaining user’s consent. 

Links to other websites

This website may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Elysium Labs Private Limited. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of these websites. We strongly recommend that when you leave our website do read the privacy statements of each and every website which collects your personal information. 

Changes in this Privacy Statement

In case, we change our privacy policy, we will post all such changes to this page and other places we deem appropriate. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time.
